本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
啊  暑假到啦
Ah, summer break...
-宝贝  你要在这上面加芝士吗  -好啊  汉克
- You want cheese on that hon? - Sure, Hank.
现在是休闲  娱乐
A time for leisure, recreation,
跟放松的时间
and takin' 'er easy...
除非你是我
Unless you're me.
它要追上来了
It's getting closer!
我叫迪普
My name is Dipper.
这个快要呕吐的女孩是我的姐姐梅宝
The girl about to puke is my sister Mabel.
你或许在好奇为什么我们正开着高尔夫球车飞奔
You may be wondering what we're doing in a golf cart
逃避一只不可思议的恐怖生物
fleeing from a creature of unimaginable horror.
-小心  -啊
- Look out! - Aahh!
放心  我有一个完美的合理解释
Rest assured, there's a perfectly logical explanation.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： Sarina
校订： WaitinZ
■
后期： WaitinZ  leland
怪诞小镇  第一季第一集
Gravity Falls  S01E01  Tourist Trapped
我们先倒带
Let's rewind.
这一切要从父母决定让我们出趟远门说起
It all began when our parents decided we could use some fresh air.
他们把我们送到北方俄勒冈州
They shipped us up north to a sleepy town
一个叫做重力泉的寂静小镇
called Gravity Falls, Oregon,
好让我们住在叔公深山野林里的家
to stay at our great-uncle's place in the woods.
这阁楼太赞了
This attic is amazing!
看看我手上扎的刺
Check out all my splinters!
而且我床上还有只山羊
And there's a goat on my bed.
嗨  朋友
Hey, friend.
噢  你就放心咬我的毛衣吧  哈哈
Oh! Yes, you can keep chewing on my sweater. Ha ha ha ha ha!
我的姐姐总试着往好的方面看
My sister tended to look on the bright side of things.
耶  青草地
Yay! Grass!
但是为了适应新环境
But I was having a hard time
我可是受尽了苦头
getting used to our new surroundings.
这就是我们的叔公斯坦
And then was our great-uncle Stan...
就是这家伙
that guy.
还是值了
It was worth it.
叔公把他的房子改装成一个叫做神秘小屋的
Our uncle had transformed his house into a tourist trap
专门敲诈旅客的景点
he called the Mystery Shack.
但是真正神秘的问题是为什么还有大批的人来参观
The real mystery was why anyone came.
女士们  先生们  请看
Ladies and gentlemen, behold...
体毛怪
the sascrotch!
-哇哦  -我的天哪
- Whoa! - Oh, my gosh!
猜猜谁要在这里工作吧
And guess who had to work there.
不许碰商品
No touching the merchandise!
本以为整个夏天都会是一成不变无聊日子
It looked like it was gonna be the same boring routine all summer
直到这么一个重大的日子
until one fateful day...
他正在读信  他正在读信
He's looking at it. He's looking at it!
你喜欢我吗
"Do you like me?
是的  当然
"Yes. Definitely.
肯定
Absolutely"?
-我干的  -梅宝
- I rigged it! - Mabel,
我知道你正在经历花痴的阶段
I know you're going through your whole "Boy crazy" Phase,
但是我觉得你有点痴迷过度了
But I think you're kind of overdoing it with the "Crazy" part.
什么
What?!
拜托了  迪普
Come on, Dipper!
这是我第一个离家的暑假
This is our first summer away from home.
是我展开史诗般的夏日浪漫史的重大机会
It's my big chance to have an epic summer romance.
我知道  但是你有必要跟每一个你遇见的男生打情骂俏么
Yeah, but do you need to flirt with every guy you meet?
我叫做梅宝  但是你可以叫我梦中女神
My name is Mabel, but you can call me the girl of your dreams.
我在开玩笑啦  哈哈哈哈
I'm joking! Ha ha ha ha!
我的天哪  你喜欢乌龟
Oh, my gosh, you like turtles?
我也喜欢乌龟  这到底是怎么回事啊
I like turtles too. What is happening here?
来吧  大家都来吧
Come one, come all,
来看超值王子床垫啊
to the mattress prince's kingdom of savings!
-带我走吧  -啊
- Take me with you. - Aaah!
随你怎么嘲笑我  老哥
Mock all you want, brother,
但是我对这个暑假有很好的预感
but I got a good feeling about this summer.
如果我的梦中情人现在从那扇门走进来
I wouldn't be surprised if the man of my dreams
我也不会惊讶
walked through that door right now.
噢 噢  真不舒服  噢
Oh! Oh! Not good. Ow.
-哎  为什么  -哈哈哈
- Oh, why?! - Ha ha ha!
好了好了  大家打起精神
All right, all right, look alive, people.
谁跟我去森林深处
I need someone to go hammer
把这些指示牌钉上
up these signs in the spooky part of the forest.
-不是我  -不是我
- Not it! - Not it!
呃  也不是我
Uh, also not it.
没人叫你  苏斯
Nobody asked you, Soos.
我知道  而且我没意见
I know, and I'm comfortable with that.
温迪  我需要你去钉上这些指示牌
Wendy! I need you to put up this sign!
我也想  但是我  呃  够不着
I would, but I... uhh... can't... uhh... reach it.
我真想把你们全部辞掉
I'd fire all of you if I could.
好吧  那我们就挑兵挑将吧
All right, let's make it eeny-meeny-miney...
-你去  -噢  不是吧
- You. - Oh! What?
斯坦叔公  每次去深林
Grunkle Stan, whenever I'm
我都感觉被监视着一样
in those woods I feel like I'm being watched.
-哎  又来了  -我要告诉你
- Ahh, this again. - I'm telling you,
这小镇上有些诡异的事情正在发生
Something weird is going on in this town.
今天蚊子在我身上咬了“当心”的字样
Just today my mosquito bites spelled out "Beware."
那是  当丁
That says "Bewarb."
听着  小子  深林怪物的故事
Look, kid, the whole "Monsters
只是我这种家伙鼓吹出来的本地传说
in the forest" thing is just local legend
目的是把商品卖给那种笨家伙
drummed up by guys like me to sell merch to guys like that.
所以不要再疑神疑鬼了
So quit being so paranoid!
哎  斯坦叔公
Ugh. Grunkle Stan.
没人相信我说的话
Nobody ever believes anything I say.
通往神秘小屋
搞什么
What the...?
真难以相信我研究俄勒冈州重力泉的
"It's hard to believe it's been six years since I began studying
奇闻怪事已达六年之久
the strange and wondrous secrets of Gravity Falls, Oregon."
浮动的眼球
巨型
吸血蝙蝠
矮人
这些都是什么
What is all this?
很不幸  我的怀疑被证实了
"Unfortunately, my suspicions have been confirmed.
我被监视了
"I'm being watched.
我必须赶在被他发现之前把这本书藏起来
"I must hide this book before he finds it.
记住  在重力泉  不能相信任何人
Remember, in Gravity Falls, there is no one you can trust."
不能相信任何人
No one you can trust...
-嗨  -啊
- Hello! - Aaah!
你在看什么  书呆子看的东西吗
Whatcha readin'? Some nerd thing?
呃 呃  什么都没有
Uh... uh... it's nothing.
"Uh-uh... it's nothing."
干嘛  你真的不打算给我看吗
What? Are you actually not gonna show me?
呃  我们去个隐秘点的地方吧
Uh, let's go somewhere private.
这真是太棒了
It's amazing!
斯坦叔公说我疑神疑鬼
Grunkle Stan said I was being paranoid,
但是根据这本书
but according to this book,
重力泉真的隐藏着一些黑暗的秘密
Gravity Falls has this secret dark side.
哇哦  不是吧
Whoa! Shut up!
而且在看了好几页后
and get this, after a certain point,
记载就停止了
the pages just stop,
就好像作者离奇失踪了
like the guy who was writing it mysteriously disappeared.
谁啊
Who's that?
好吧  是时候坦白了
Well, time to spill the beans.
这儿  豆子
Broop. Beans.
我有个约会  呼呼
This girl's got a date. Whoo whoo!
-哈哈哈  -让我先弄明白
- Ha ha ha! - Let me get this straight.
你是说在我离开的半小时内  你找到了一个男朋友
In the half hour I was gone you already found a boyfriend?
我还能说什么呢
What can I say?
我猜我就是让人无法抗拒
I guess I'm just irresistible!
来啦
Coming!
-你在看什么  小屁孩  -噢
- What you readin' there, slick? - Oh!
我只是在看  呃
I was just catchin' up on, uh...
-老男人金链杂志  -这期很精彩
- "Gold chains for old men magazine"? - That's a good issue.
嗨  家人们
Hey, family!
跟我的男朋友打个招呼
Say hello to my new boyfriend!
嗨
'Sup?
-嗨  -你好啊
- Hey. - How's it hangin'.
我们是在墓地遇见的  他很有深度
We met at the cemetery. He's really deep.
噢  有一小块肌肉呢
Ooh! Little muscle there.
真惊讶啊
What... what a surprise.
那么  你叫什么名字
So what's your name?
呃  正常  人
Uh... Normal... Man!
他说“诺曼”
He means "Norman."
你是在流血吗  诺曼
Are you bleeding, Norman?
是果酱
It's jam.
噢  我喜欢果酱
Oh! I love jam!
你看你们我们多般配
Look at this!
那么  你想去牵牵手  或者随便干点什么吗
So, you wanna go hold hands or... whatever?
噢  我的老天
Oh! Oh, my goodness.
别等我们了
Don't wait up!
这个诺曼有些不对劲
There was something about Norman that wasn't right.
我决定翻阅一下这本日志
I decided to consult the journal...
因他们苍白的皮肤和差劣的态度而闻名
"Known for their pale skin and bad attitudes,
这些生物常常被误认为  青少年
"These creatures are often mistaken for... Teenagers?!
留心怪诞小镇的邪恶
"Beware Gravity Falls's nefarious...
嗨
'Sup?
丧尸
Zombie!"
刚刚有人讲框尸吗  什么是框尸
Did somebody say "Cromby"? What is that, "Cromby"?
根本没有这个字  你快疯了吧
It's not even a word. You're losin' your mind.
我喜欢你
I like you.
噢 不  梅宝
Oh, no! Mabel!
-不不  梅宝  小心  -呃
- No! No, Mabel! Watch out! - Uhh!
雏菊
Daisies?
你这淘气鬼
You scallywag!
我的姐姐真的在跟一个丧尸约会吗
Is my sister really dating a zombie,
还是我疯了
or am I just going nuts?
这诚然是个左右为难的处境啊
It's a dilemma, to be sure.
我不自禁听到你
I couldn't help but overhear
在这间空房子里大声自言自语
you talking aloud to yourself in this empty room.
苏斯  你见过梅宝的男朋友
Soos, you've seen Mabel's boyfriend.
他肯定是个丧尸  对吧
He's gotta be a zombie, right?
呃  你看见那家伙吃过多少个脑袋
Hmm. How many brains did you see the guy eat?
-一个也没有  -听着  伙计  我相信你
- Zero. - Look, dude, I believe you.
我总是注意到这个小镇里的怪事
I'm always noticing weird stuff in this town.
例如那个邮差  我非常确信那家伙是个狼人
Like the mailman? Pretty sure that dude's a werewolf.
但是你必须拿出证据
But you gotta have evidence.
不然大家只觉得
Otherwise people are gonna
你是个职棒联盟里不起眼的破钟表
think you're a major league cuckoo clock.
苏斯  又被你说对了
As always, Soos, you're right.
我的智慧既是祝福也是诅咒
My wisdom is both a blessing and a curse.
苏斯  移动厕所又堵了
Soos! The portable toilets are clogged again!
别处需要我
I am needed elsewhere.
我姐姐可能遇到麻烦了
My sister could be in trouble.
是时候找出证据了
It was time to get some evidence.
我看够了
I'd seen enough.
梅宝  我们必须谈谈诺曼
Mabel, we've gotta talk about Norman.
他真是太棒了  对吧  你看他给我烙上的大唇印
Isn't he the best? Check out this giant smooch mark he gave me!
大笨蛋  只是用吹叶机的时候出了点小意外
Gullible. It was just an accident with the leaf blower.
接吻练习
Kissing practice!
啊  把它关上
Aah! Turn it off!
把它关上
Turn it off!
-真有趣  -不  梅宝  听着
- That was fun. - No! Mabel, listen.
我想告诉你那不是诺曼的真面目
I'm trying to tell you that Norman is not what he seems!
你觉得他可能是个吸血鬼
You think he might be a vampire?
要真那样就太棒啦
That would be so awesome!
再猜一遍  姐姐
Guess again, sister.
-看  -啊
- Sha-bam! - Aaah!
哦  不是  抱歉
Oh, wait. I'm... I'm sorry.
-看  -丧尸
- Sha-bam! - A zombie?
这一点也不好玩  迪普
That is not funny, Dipper.
我没有开玩笑
I'm not joking!
所有的一切都合情合理  血液  还有瘸脚
It all adds up: the bleeding, the limp...
他从来不眨眼  你注意到了吗
He never blinks! Have you noticed that?
或许他跟你同一时间眨眼
Maybe he's blinking when you're blinking.
梅宝  记得书中是怎么记载重力泉的吗
Mabel, remember what the book said about Gravity Falls?
不要相信任何人
"Trust no one"!
那我呢  你为什么不能相信我呢
What about me, huh? Why can't you trust me?
-哔哔  -梅宝
- Beep-bop! - Mabel!
他会吃掉你的脑袋的
He's gonna eat your brain!
迪普  听我说
Dipper, listen to me.
诺曼跟我五点还有个约会
Norman and I are going on a date at five o'clock,
而且我会表现得很可爱  他则会很完美
and I'm gonna be adorable, and he's gonna be dreamy.
-等一下  但 但 但  -而且我不会让你的疯狂诡计
- Wait! But... but... but... - And I'm not gonna let you ruin it
毁了我的约会
with one of your crazy conspiracies!
哦  我该怎么办
Ohh. What am I gonna do?
来了
Coming!
嗨  诺曼  我看起来怎样
Hey, Norman. How do I look?
闪闪发光
Shiny!
你一直这么会说话
You always know what to say!
苏斯说得对
Soos is right.
我没有任何证据
I don't have any real evidence.
我猜我有时确实有点多疑了
I guess I can be kind of paranoid sometimes, and...
等一下  不是吧
Wait! What?!
啊  我是对的  天哪
Aaah! I was right! Oh, my God!
我的天哪  斯坦叔公  斯坦叔公  斯坦叔公
Oh, my God! Grunkle Stan! Grunkle Stan! Grunkle Stan!
这就是那块像脸的石头
And here we have "Rock that looks like a face" Rock...
名叫“像脸的石头”
the rock that looks like a face.
-它看起来像石头吗  -不  它看起来像脸
- Does it look like a rock? - No, it looks like a face.
-它是张脸吗  -它是一块像脸的石头
- Is it a face? - It's a rock that looks like a face!
这里  斯坦叔公
Over here! Grunkle Stan!
说第五遍了  它不是一张真正的脸
For the fifth time, it's not an actual face!
我们终于能单独待会儿了
Finally, we're alone.
是啊  单独
Yes... Alone.
斯坦  斯坦
Stan! Stan!
温蒂  温蒂
Wendy! Wendy!
我需要借用高尔夫球车
I need to borrow the golf
好从丧尸手上救回我姐姐
cart so I can save my sister from a zombie!
记住不要撞到行人
Try not to hit any pedestrians.
伙计  是我  苏斯
Dude, it's me, Soos.
-这是给你干掉丧尸用的  -谢了
- This is for the zombies. - Thanks.
这是给你万一见到糖果罐时用的
And this is in case you see a pinata.
呃  多谢了
Uh... Thanks?
还是小心为妙啊
Better safe than sorry!
梅宝
Mable,
现在我们已经互相有些了解了
now that we've gotten to know each other,
有些
there's...
有些事情我必须告诉你
There's something I should tell you.
噢  诺曼  你可以告诉我任何事情
Oh, Norman! You can tell me anything!
拜托是吸血鬼  拜托是吸血鬼
Please be a vampire, please be a vampire.
好的  就是  就是不要害怕  好吗
All right, just... just don't freak out, okay?
只要  只要保持开放的心态  沉着冷静
Just... just keep an open mind. Be cool.
这奇怪吗  这是不是太奇怪啦
Is this weird? Is this too weird?
你需要坐下来吗
You need to sit down?
好吧  我会解释清楚的
R-right. I'll explain.
那个  我们是小矮人  首先要知道这一点
So, we're gnomes, first off, get that one out of the way.
-呃  -我叫杰夫
- Uh... - I'm Jeff,
他们是卡森  斯蒂夫
and here we have Carson, Steve,
詹森  跟
Jason and...
对不起  我老是忘记你的名字
I'm sorry, I always forget your name.
史麦布莱克
Shmebulock.
史麦布莱克  对
Shmebulock. Yes!
好了  长话短说
Anyways, long story short,
我们小矮人正在找一个新女王  对吧  伙计们
us gnomes have been lookin' for a new queen. Right, guys?
女王  女王
Queen! Queen!
你觉得怎样
Heh! So whaddya say?
你愿意跟我们结为夫福吗
Will you join us in holy matri-gnome-y?
夫  夫妇
Matri... matri... mony?
哎  紧张得不会说话了
Bleahh! Can't talk today.
这个
Look...
对不起  伙计们  你们都非常可爱
I'm sorry, guys, you're really sweet,
但是我是一个女孩  而你们是小矮人
but I'm a girl and you're gnomes
这种结合就像  搞什么
and it's like, "What?!"
哎呀
Yikes.
我们明白  我们永远不会忘记你的  梅宝
We understand. We'll never forget you, Mabel.
-因为我们要绑架你  -什么
- Because we're gonna kidnap you. - Huh?!
别担心  梅宝  我会把你从丧尸的手中救出来
Don't worry, Mabel! I'll save you from that zombie!
救命
Help!!!!
坚持住
Hold on!
你越挣扎
The more you struggle,
这事情对大家来说就越难办
the more awkward this is gonna be for everybody.
哈哈  抓住她的手臂  斯蒂夫
Just... ha ha!... Okay, just get her arm there, Steve.
啊  放开我
Aah! Let go of me!
这到底是怎么回事
What the heck is goin' on here?!
迪普  诺曼原来是五个小矮人扮的
Dipper! Norman turned out to be a bunch of gnomes!
而且他们都是十足的坏蛋
And they're total jerks!
啊  头发  头发
Uhh! Hair! Hair!
小矮人  呃  我错得厉害
Gnomes? Huh. I was way off.
小矮人  重力泉深林里的侏儒
"Gnomes. Little men of the Gravity Falls forest.
弱点  未知
"Weaknesses:" Unknown.
哎  不是吧
Oh, come on!
喂喂  放开我的姐姐
Hey! Hey! Let go of my sister!
哦  哈哈  你好啊  呃  你懂的
Oh! Ha ha. Hey there! Um, ya know,
这只是个大误会  是这样的
this is all really just a big misunderstanding, ya see?
你的姐姐没有处于危险中
Your sister's not in danger...
她只是会跟我们一千个小矮人结婚
She's just marrying all one thousand of us
然后变成矮人女王直到永远
and become our gnome queen for all eternity.
我说得对吧 宝贝
Isn't that right, honey?
你们放屁
You guys are butt-faces!
马上放开她 否则我就不客气了
Give her back right now, or else!
你觉得你能阻止我们吗  小子
You think you can stop us, boy?
你根本不知道我们有多厉害
You have no idea what we're capable of.
小矮人是强大的种群
The gnomes are a powerful race!
不要小看
Do not trifle with the...
他要跟我们的女王逃跑
He's getting away with our queen!
不不不
No, no, no!!!
系好安全带
Seat belt.
你惹错人了  小子
You've messed with the wrong creatures, boy.
深林里的矮人们  集合
Gnomes of the forest... Assemble!
快点  他们要赶上我们了
Hurry! Before they come after us!
我可不担心
I wouldn't worry about it.
看见他们的小细腿了吗  窝囊废就是小
You see their little legs? Suckers are tiny.
该死
Dang.
好了  兄弟们齐心协力  就像我们训练的那样
All right, teamwork, guys! Like we practiced.
走  快走
Move. Move!
-女王回来  -它们要追上来了
- Come back with our queen! - It's getting closer!
史麦布莱克
Shmebulock!
我来救你  迪普
I'll save you, Dipper!
-谢了  梅宝  -不客气
- Thanks, Mabel. - Don't mention it.
小心
Look out!
别过来
Stay back, man!
斯坦叔公在哪
Where's Grunkle Stan?
注意啦
Behold!
世界上最让人分神的东西
The world's most distracting object!
-噢  -试试转移目光  你就是做不到
- Oooh! - Just try to look away... you can't!
我连自己讲什么都忘了
I can't even remember what I was talkin' about.
到墙角啦  孩子们
It's the end of the line, kids.
梅宝  你最好在我们干坏事前答应结婚
Mabel, marry us before we do something crazy!
肯定还有办法逃出去的
There's gotta be a way out of this!
-我必须这么做  -什么
- I gotta do it. - What?!
梅宝  不要啊  你疯了吗
Mabel, don't do this! Are you crazy?
-相信我  -什么
- Trust me. - What?!
迪普  就这一次  相信我
Dipper, just this once... Trust me.
-好了  杰夫  我答应跟你结婚  -耶
- All right, Jeff, I'll marry you. - Hot dog!
放我下来  詹森  谢了  安迪  左脚
Help me down there, Jason. Thanks. Andy, left foot,
这就对了  小心手指  麦克
there we go, watch those fingers, Mike.
啊  怎么样
Ehh? Ehh?
好耶  好耶
Bada-Bing, bada-bam!
现在我们一起回深林吧  亲爱的
Now let's get you back into the forest, honey!
你现在可以亲吻新娘了
You may now kiss the bride.
呃  这样也好
Well, uh, don't mind if I do.
喂  等一下  啊啊
Hey, wait a minute! Ahh-aahh...
喔  喔  怎么回事
Whoa! Whoa! W-what's going on?
这是因为你骗了我
That's for lying to me!
这是因为你让我心碎
That's for breaking my heart!
啊  我的脸
Ow! My face!
这是因为你招惹了我弟弟
And this is for messing with my brother!
-想尽地主之谊吗  -数三声
- Wanna do the honors? - On three.
一  二  三
One, two, three!
我会回来报仇的
I'll... Get you back for this!!!!!
谁来指挥  我需要指挥
Who's giving orders? I need orders!
我的手臂好累
My arms are tired!
谁还想试试
Anyone else wants some?
那个  迪普  我
Hey, Dipper. I, um,
对不起我无视了你的意见
I'm sorry for ignoring your advice.
你其实只是在关心我
You really were just looking out for me.
噢  别这样说  你刚刚救了我呢
Oh, don't be like that. You saved our butts back there.
我猜我只是因为我的初恋男友
I guess I'm just sad that my first boyfriend
原来是几个小矮人而伤心
turned out to be a bunch of gnomes.
乐观点儿  或许下一个就是吸血鬼呢
Look on the bright side... Maybe the next one will be a vampire.
你也就是说说而已
You're just saying that.
褰愕鼙П
Awkward sibling hug?
Awkward sibling hug.
-拍拍  -拍拍
- Pat pat. - Pat pat.
天哪  你们两个被车撞了还是怎么了
Sheesh! You two get hit by a bus or somethin'?
喂
Uh, hey!
你们知道吗
W-wouldn't you know it?
呃  我不小心多买了存货
Um, I accidentally overstocked some inventory,
所以不如你们两个
so how's about each of you
在礼品屋里挑件礼物
take one item from the gift shop on the house?
-真的吗  -有什么条件
- Really? - What's the catch?
条件就是在我改变主意前选  现在去挑样东西
The catch is do it before I change my mind. Now take something.
嗯  这帽子不错
Hmm. That oughta do the trick.
那我就挑个
And I will have a...
爪钩
Grappling hook!
-好啊  -你为什么不挑个布娃娃什么的
- Yes! - Wouldn't you rather have a doll or something?
-爪钩  -好吧
- Grappling hook! - Fair enough.
这本日记告诉我在怪诞小镇重力泉
"This journal told me there was no one in Gravity Falls
不能相信任何人
"I could trust.
但是当你跟某人肩并肩
"But when you battle a hundred gnomes
与上百个小矮人作战的时候
"Side-by-side with someone,
你意识到他们或许会永远支持你
you realize that they've probably always got your back."
嗨  梅宝  能帮忙关下灯吗
Hey, Mabel, could you get the light?
我这就来
I'm on it.
成功了
It worked!
-哈哈哈  -这爪钩
- Ha ha ha! - These grappling hooks...
叔公告诉我们这小镇没有任何怪事
Our uncle told us there was nothing strange about this town.
但谁知道还有其他什么秘密
But who knows what other secrets
正等待我们去揭开呢
are waiting to be unlocked?